Hello everyone, the CLOSE 2024.1 version is about to meet you.
The new features are fully upgraded to make your experience more convenient.
This video will take you through a new version of the update from the point of view of clothing development.
Including UI updates, file preparation, file editing, design, production, display, and the final one-stop cooperation in the Closet.
Without further ado, let's take a look.
First of all, we have optimized the UI.
One of the biggest changes is that in the main menu at the top, you will now see the option to produce, connect, and Closet.
Therefore, you can directly visit here or upload files to Closet.
You can upload project files, clothing, or virtual models.
After the file has been modified, you can also upload the updated version.
If you need to use the Everywhere function and upload files,
you can find it in the Connect option.
You can also see that the Everywhere UI has been updated.
In the production option, you can find the function of coloring, material list, and checking the code.
In the material, you can find the material generator.
In the virtual model, you can find the virtual model editor and other related functions.
In addition, in the library window, we have added a new virtual model file folder, Mantel Human.
You can directly double-click to import and use Closet.
At the moment, we do not support directly editing the size in Closet.
You can choose to change the size and gender of the Mantel Human virtual model in the map window on the left.
Regarding virtual models,
Connect has also updated some faceless children virtual models.
You can edit the size of them in the virtual model editor.
In the new version, the UI of the virtual model editor has also been updated.
First of all, you can use the single click to drag the virtual model to the actual line.
To change the measurement position and the measurement value.
After the adjustment, you can also right-click to reset the position or reset all positions.
In this way, we can adjust the size according to the need to edit these measurement values.
In the right editor, you can set different types of measurement values that you want to check or hide.
In the width size, you can set a total width first.
For example, set a lower-body size.
You can also choose whether to set the width value.
You can set the width value and the measurement value of the width below to be linked.
Linking means that when adjusting the total width value,
the measurement value below will be adjusted to a certain extent to adapt to the total width.
Then you can adjust the size of the chest again,
so that the outline of the chest is more natural and real.
In addition, you can now control the width of the female and male models,
which is to adjust the width between the thighs of the legs,
to make them bigger or smaller.
In the male model bucket, you can change the width of the thighs,
and you can also change the size of the thighs.
In the same way, the male model can also drag the measurement line on the body to modify the size.
Set up the virtual model.
Next, we can import the costume for editing.
Select a file in the close-up resource library.
Right-click to open the previous version of this style,
and load it into the work area.
Come to the 2D window, you can edit the version below.
First, switch to the black and white surface view,
find the sewing tool in the 2D tool bar,
then add a seam allowance to the seam allowance.
You can see that one of the updates is that the seam allowance will automatically be cut into the seam allowance.
This can be applied to larger seam allowance types.
If you want the seam allowance to display different types of seam allowance,
you just need to click on the seam allowance shortcut.
You can see that there are different folding types in the attribute editor download menu.
You can choose.
Next, look at the back.
You can see that there is a basic line in the middle of the seam allowance at the bottom of the back piece.
Therefore, now, even if you use the seam allowance transfer tool to turn the seam,
the new seam allowance in the middle will also retain the basic line.
Continue to use the production source order line tool to adjust the bottom.
Divide the panels,
then use the extension panel tool to extend the back piece.
The extension panel tool after the update can also be extended to the symmetrical panel,
which is more convenient.
Since the two sides can only be extended outward,
it is impossible to change the direction.
However, you can edit the length of the upper and lower lines separately.
Click OK to extend the panel.
Complete all the editing and modification operations.
Let's check the seam allowance type again.
After updating, we can easily open or close the folding option through the secondary selection window.
And you can use the shortcut key, the single icon key next to the return key on the keyboard,
to make it more convenient to switch between the folding and the seam allowance.
After completing the edit and sewing of the panel,
we can see the seam allowance on the clothing.
We can edit it according to our needs.
When selecting the button,
under the width of the mouse pointer,
you can see the option to add the face button and the eye button.
Click to open.
At this time, change the size of the button,
and the size of the eye button will be adjusted accordingly.
If you are very satisfied with the clothes you made,
you can add it to your model library.
Open the model library,
find the group that you want to store the clothing model.
At this time, you can see that the right upper corner of the model library
has added an automatic label button.
It can automatically mark the panels in the correct model library.
If there is a leak,
we can also select the category of the component,
then select the corresponding panel,
press Enter to return to the car,
and you can quickly set it up.
Finally, click OK,
and you can find them in the model library.
As for the remaining models,
you can also update the style and name.
All you need to do is right-click on the component
and click Edit Style,
and you can modify the name and shrink chart.
Once you modify it,
the name of the original component will also be changed as you go.
Insert this pleated vest and select the fabric.
The current clothing type is wool.
There is a new option below,
and the bone line is mixed randomly.
When you open it,
you will see that the color in the fabric will be more random.
You can also control the randomness
by sliding, sliding, or entering numbers.
You can also use random variables to get different results.
In addition,
the function of adjusting the direction of the wool is also added.
You can adjust the direction of the wool
by sliding, sliding, or entering numbers.
CLO supports sRGB format now.
Open the sRGB sticker created by PS in CLO.
The color will be more consistent.
Here, insert an inner top shirt,
and add sRGB stickers on it.
This sticker was created in PS.
At this time,
you can see that the color displayed in CLO
and the color in PS remain the same height.
On the contrary,
the sRGB sticker from CLO is also the same color.
Next, let's make a jeans.
A sticker is added to the jeans.
Select the sticker,
you can see that the property editor
added a new option below the line chart.
Use the same as the plant.
Click on the button,
you can apply the hair line picture of the jeans fabric to the sticker.
After opening,
you can see that the sticker also applies the hair line effect of the jeans.
And if you select the jeans fabric,
adjust the hair line intensity,
the hair line effect of the sticker will also change.
Below this picture,
transparent picture,
and other 3D stickers,
there is also an option to use the same as the plant.
In addition,
the sticker also adds a preset type.
Click on the download menu,
you can see that the default is digital print.
Then it is the uniform,
retrofitting,
and the gold.
The gold color can be modified.
Choose to mix with the plant,
the sticker will apply all 3D stickers of the plant.
You can see that at this time,
the same options for using and planting
are in the open state below the 3D sticker.
Another update about the sticker is
to click on the sticker in the object window,
the property editor can see that
there is no other 3D sticker,
there is only a texture picture at the moment.
Click on the automatically generate button,
you can easily and quickly generate other 3D stickers,
and the generated stickers can be stored separately.
The plant can also use the option of automatically generating 3D stickers.
Next,
let's take a look at the update about the color of the flag.
We have created a more diverse system,
so that you can set more color options flexibly.
Now, when you add a flag color,
you can add a flag color that only adjusts to the material,
a flag color that only adjusts to all properties,
or you can set the information of the flag color of the related materials.
For example, you can create a flag color that only adjusts to the material,
you can modify the color, texture, and size.
You can also add ink,
and set the display of the sticker, etc.
Or you can also choose
to set all the material properties of a flag color separately,
so that you can modify its texture information and physical properties separately.
By using the new flag color function,
you can use the above settings
to view and edit clothes more freely during the work process.
The measurement tool in the new version has also been optimized.
You can now switch between different modes by clicking the shortcut key P.
A mode is the one that allows you to change the color,
and a mode is the one that allows you to measure the length of the outside of the panel.
You can operate it along the outer outline of the panel,
just like the operation of the free sewing tool.
Another mode is the straight line length measurement,
which is measured inside the panel.
You can also create a free straight line inside and outside the panel.
All measurement values will be displayed in the object window.
Now you can also more conveniently edit the code of the sticker.
When you enter the code for the sticker,
use the edit code tool to select the sticker,
and in the attribute editor,
you can choose the number of percent or unit
to decide how to change the size of the code.
When using the number of percent,
you don't have to know exactly the size of each size of the sticker,
which is more convenient.
Or use the edit code tool.
Now you can do the inner line refitting on the panel
to achieve different ways of matching the code.
When looking at the code,
we added a full mirror mode,
which allows you to see all the sizes in one picture.
It is more convenient to observe the difference between the sizes.
You can adjust the rotation of the X-axis to see the angles of the clothes,
and you can also adjust the distance between each size.
And we can also use this mode
to see the pressure and force of the clothes.
Finally, you can output the clothes rendering image.
First, open the style image rendering in the 3D vertical menu.
Now you can see the chain and the component in the style image rendering.
This makes the style effect picture of the clothes more complete.
Next, click on the virtual model.
Find the sample modifier in the property editor.
You can now quickly modify the color of the virtual model's eyes.
After the modification is complete,
you can also click on the reset or keep the changes you made.
In addition, for the simulation picture,
you can now reduce the particle diameter of the simulation picture
to less than 1 mm.
A warning window will pop up when you modify it.
This will be very serious to the memory consumption
and there is a risk of flashback.
If you want to continue, you can click on Yes.
A lower particle diameter can make your picture look more realistic.
You can open the rendering window to check the rendering effect.
In addition, in the rendering window,
you can see a new option in the rendering tool bar.
Lock the rendering view.
In this way, we can edit the lighting in the 3D window
and keep the viewing angle of the rendering window unchanged.
And you can check the effect after the lighting adjustment in the rendering window.
In addition, you can also output multi-view rendering images.
In the image property, select the custom view.
In the bottom of the save,
an option for merging the whole scene is added.
Click on Open.
The final rendering will be received.
You can see the rendering image of each angle
and the merged rendering image.
After the rendering is completed,
we can also do AI face-to-face integration.
This is a highlight feature of this update.
Click on the magic stick button in the tool bar on the right side.
Enter the AI model workshop.
You can see that the just rendered image will appear here automatically.
Of course, you can also upload other pictures.
Then, by setting gender, age and race,
randomly generate keywords or manually input keywords,
to automatically generate a reference image for face-to-face integration.
Then click on Start Rendering to wait for the result.
The pictures after rendering will appear on the right side.
You can also save the pictures.
In addition, we can also use real-time photos to do AI face-to-face integration.
After completing the 3D file in Clo,
you can upload it to the original platform CloSat for one-stop writing.
In addition, you can also use the original platform CloSat for one-stop writing.
If you are a new user,
you can visit our website and sign up for a new account.
In CloSat,
you can upload and share your 3D file with others anytime.
With the current support,
you can upload multiple files at the same time,
and you can drag the file directly to the workshop to make the operation more convenient.
In the content page,
you can also browse the uploaded files using the 3D reader.
You can also see the career pictures of the costume.
You can also mark and comment, which is convenient for you to communicate and coordinate with other users.
In addition, you can also use your 3D assets to create visual articles using the new function of Cross-Site.
In the visual reading board, you can match different content, such as 3D clothing, fabric, clothes, color board, etc. to show your design and concept.
In the visual reading board, users can check 3D clothing through the link and share the visual reading board with others through the link.
The above is the main function of this update.
Thank you for your warm response and support, which helps us to continue to improve and grow.
We will also release a separate function to explain the video later.
So if you want to learn more about a certain function, you can follow our official account.
Thank you for watching.